Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
What is Alişar Bey talking about for this
long? I hope he's not bothering my Sheikh.
If he bothers my father, he would
kindly make him go. Don't you worry.
Mother, stop, mother. Don't you
have anyone to help you out?
Oh, Alişar Bey, you don't have
to worry about me, thank you.
Help this mother to her home.
May Allah bless you, are
there still people like you?
A Bey whose people are not
peaceful, can not have prosperity.
- You just don't forget us when you pray.
- May Allah bless you.
Listen to me, from now on,
there will be food at noontime.
It will be served to the poor
in the marketplace for free.
May it be easy, Bala Hatun.
Thank you, Alişar Bey.
Mashallah, Mashallah.
You've made such beauties with your hands.
Even your one little smile is
a pleasure for me, Bala Hatun.
Tawbah!
Bala Hatun.
You look the other way,
but I want you to understand.
I want you to be the Sultan
of my heart's mansion.
I have the world's most beautiful trouble.
But, even being ruined by
your hands is beautiful.
I want you to know...
I opened my heart to your
father, he didn't allow it.
But I will wait.
A smile, a look will be the seeds
of hope for my garden of union.
You are forcing, Alişar Bey. A garden
without consent can't have flowers.
I will wait, Bala Hatun.
While I wait, I will say...
"Oh, the face of heaven...
"I am so busy with you..."
... that I can't even remember myself."
You are going too far, Alişar Bey.
I said my words. There is no beyond.
My Bey, we've ruined Gündüz as you
commanded. He should be in the Tent now.
Then let's go and say our
best wishes to him.
So that they know Alişar Bey's wrath!
Osman.
He is the antichrist.
He threw me to the hands of Alişar.
Ma'am, Alişar won't let this go.
We've gotten into Alişar's mind
with Master Yannis' help, Helen.
From now on, he will serve us...
... with his every decision.
Balances are very fragile.
Even a hair's weight matters.
Master Yannis will inform us after
he's done with his calculations.
From now on...
... all roads will lead to Abul
for Alişar.
Peace be upon you!
Peace be upon you too!
-Sergeant Samsa!
-Osman Bey!
Samsa Bey.
- Sergeant Samsa!
- Konur!
My Bey.
People should fear you.
You pierced the mountain.
Running water wouldn't be in moss.
Osman Bey isn't running,
he's gushing, Mashallah.
We are just beginning, brothers.
With Allah's help, we will crush
down every obstacle before us.
Inshallah.
Are you hungry, my lion?
Here, my Bey.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
The first obstacle is Alişar, my Bey.
As long as we stand united, back to back,
no one can stand in our way.
About Alişar, he must
be close to the Tent.
He's thinking about
getting respect from Kayı.
- Come on.
- Sit here, Abdurrahman Gazi.
- How is he, Hatun?
- His heart beats slowly.
I didn't say it to Ayşe Hatun, but he's
not doing well, my Bey.
I took all four arrows, but...
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Alişar Bey is coming to
our Tent with his soldiers.
Alişar will try to threaten the Kayıs.
Dündar Bey will get very angry when
he learns that we took the gold.
My uncle's loyalty to Kayı is
out of question.
But he lacks caution.
He can't see ahead.
He'll think that we're bandits as well.
But he's not wrong, my Bey.
He doesn't know that the gold
is coming from the Mongols.
But he knows that Alişar
is the Mongols' dog.
He keeps obeying just so
his system isn't shaken.
We'll get through the dirty
traps one by one.
We'll take from the cruel, and
give to the poor.
Those who rebel against reach prosperity.
Now those who obey.
I heard about what happened to Gündüz.
It crushed my heart.
I'm here to say get well.
There was a cruel ambush, Alişar Bey.
How is he doing?
His wounds are deep.
- Who did it?
- We are looking for traces.
We'll figure it out soon.
But whoever did this...
... will pay a heavy price!
Stop talking nonsense, Dündar!
I made them shoot Gündüz!
- You?!
- Stop!
Ara you pillaging in my lands,
in my caravansary?
We don't pillage, Alişar Bey.
We make a holy war!
Since when ambushing and stealing
a holy war, Dündar?
Your betrayal stories are over, and now
are you blaming us with robbery?
If stealing the Banner Lord's gold isn't
a robbery, then what is it?
A valiant who steals from others,
especially from the Banner Lord...
... can't wear the Kayı's
armour, Alişar Bey!
I know each one of their names.
It's Osman's job.
Osman's doings!
Erkut.
Go to the Bazaar. There are people on
Alişar Bey's side, who serve Yannis.
Look sharp and find out who they are.
Yannis' arms are long. We need to
be one step ahead of him.
Otherwise, all our work
will be for nothing.
My Bey, do you think he has people
in the caravansary?
There are because Alişar knows
that we did it.
Then Yannis and Alişar Bey
are cooperating, my Bey.
It's too early to declare.
But it's certain that they found a way
and surrounded Alişar Bey.
We'll start preparing.
All the equipment is here.
Konur brother, you shall bring the news.
Check the weapons.
We'll enter the castle. We'll take
the gold Alişar Bey wants, and give him.
This is my last warning to Kayıs.
If Osman doesn't bring twice the gold
he stole until tomorrow...
... all of you will end up like Gündüz!
Don't do it, Alişar Bey. How can we get
so much gold in so little time?
You touch my pole, and
I'll destroy your Tent!
You break by branch, and
I'll burn your mountain!
I'm Alişar Bey! Alişar Bey!
Open your ears, and listen carefully.
If you don't bring my gold,
just to prove my point...
... I'll destroy your Tent, break your
hands, exile your women!
Know that!
Kulucahisar. Here, my Bey.
Look at Konur. He's been in every
hole like a mole.
If Osman Bey didn't make us go there
before, they'd have hunted us like birds.
Sofia is alert. They hold everywhere.
My Bey. There's a hole between
the side walls.
We can get in through there.
We can get through.
But how will we get inside from there?
What if we use the barrels again, my Bey?
You don't stab the enemy
from the same place, my Baran.
I know a secret route.
We can get inside without anyone noticing.
You're on a streak, Sıddık.
That secret route won't
be our dungeon, will it?
Sıddık's promise, Osman Bey.
I'll take you to the gold.
Osman! Look what you did to us!
Osman left saying he'd look for traces.
I think he knew Alişar was coming here...
... he didn't want to embarrass himself.
It's not the first time.
We're out of patience, my Bey!
Either tame Osman or exile him!
Or the entire Tent
will disappear because of him!
Zöhre! Slow down, you're going too fast!
Dündüz is fighting for his life in
the other room.
The entire Tent is in danger and you're
still defending Osman!
How many times did Osman not
stand for his word...
... what did he do that he
couldn't explain?
Now I'm asking you. Maybe we're hurt,
maybe we'll be hurt more.
But if my Osman did something, I'm sure
he knows something!
No, Selcan Hatun!
This can't go on like this!
Osman is pushing the limits. He's my
nephew, my life, my blood...
... but if it's either Tent or Osman,
I'll choose the Tent.
His choice.
It shall refresh your heart, my father.
your sorrowful eyes are singing, father.
Your Bala shall die for you.
I remembered the merciful Prophet.
Who knows the pain he feels when
he sees the state of his people.
Who knows how much his heart aches.
The crusaders, the Mongols spilt
lots of Muslim blood.
They dishonoured us.
They hurt our dignity.
The idea of enslavement rules our hearts.
Especially the things that
invade Muslim hearts...
... grudge, hatred, betrayal, slander...
... lust.
Oh my Allah!
Who knows how much the state of
his people hurt our Prophet.
Did he endure such pain,
such oppression...
... for this?
Just so his people could pray
to their Rab in peace...
... did he endure such troubles for this?
Did he sacrifice his friends for this?
What about the things Muslims
do to other Muslims?
Just because their sects are different,
they slaughter each other.
They can't unite against cruelty.
Tomorrow in doomsday, how will we look
at our Prophet's face...
... who cried for this people,
my daughter?
How?
What you've said in the
caravansary was right, Abdul.
Now tell me, where did Osman hide my gold?
M-My Bey...
He has a secret.
We can't see it.
This information is mysterious.
What are you mumbling?
Just say it!
My Bey. The world of spirits!
I see something more valuable
than the gold, my Bey!
What is it? Tell me!
Osman's dignity in his Tent is gone!
That's it.
There will be more, my Bey!
Your magnificence scares everyone,
your power devours, my Bey!
It's near. There are
big victories on your way!
Continue.
I see the fire, the desire
inside you, my Bey!
To rule! You wish to rule entire lands!
Not Sultan's shadow, you wish to
be the Sultan himself!
I do!
Continue!
Woman of the enemy, my Bey! She looks
like your enemy...
... but she'll be your best friend!
Your desire is within her. When you unite
with her, she'll give you more power!
Your might will cross the mountains!
Sofia...
In the ninety-nine names of Allah
who has the power to create...
...and who fills our hearts with faith.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name
of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
Kayı's valiant Beys. No point in
beating around the bush.
You've all heard about
Alişar Bey's threats.
I wanted to consult you so we
could do something about it.
Osman Bey took Alişar Bey's gold. You
employed him as your primary helper.
But as I see, he isn't in the meeting.
Why doesn't he explain anything?
This has nothing to do with Osman.
It's all Alişar's doings.
The gold is coming from the Mongols.
But Demirci Bey...
... you don't say anything to Alişar,
but you are questioning Osman.
It's time we unite, and not fight.
We have to collect the amount
Alişar Bey is asking for.
Demirci Bey is talking sense, Bamsı Bey.
If Osman is responsible for this...
... he should bring the gold and rescue
us from this mess.
- He's right!
- He's right.
I believe my nephew handed
the gold out to the poor.
I don't have any hope. None.
Then we have to clean Osman's mess again.
We need to do something about Alişar.
Give the order and...
... we shall take battle positions
with my Alps, father.
A possible conflict means we'll be facing
not only Alişar...
... but also the Mongols he's obeying.
Now what we need is to calculate
everything we have that's worth gold.
Everyone should do their part.
I want to know the value of the herd, the
goods in the barn, and the fabrics.
If it's necessary, we'll
sell everything...
... but we won't let our Tent
be destroyed.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Where's that place you're talking about?
Show me.
Right here.
Behind the walls which protect the castle.
Why did you move your eyebrows?
What's on your mind?
Sergeant Samsa. If the infidels made
secret passages for leaving the castle...
... they made traps for those
who try to get in.
We're an army of eagles.
We don't fear owls.
Instead of being a husband, you look
forward to the battle, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Son, when we came to these lands
behind the scarlet tails...
... we swore on something.
Until the last drop of sweat, the last
drop of blood, the last arrow...
...in the quiver, we'll fight for Allah
and be the enemy's nightmare!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Look what Osman did to us, Selcan Hatun!
We're counting our goods and goats
to pay Alişar's gold.
I've been saying it since the beginning,
but you're not listening.
Himself isn't enough, he's going to cause
the whole Tent to be burned!
May I come in, uncle?
Come in!
How can you set your eyes on the
Banner Lord's gold, Osman?
Uncle! Those who are as straight as a die
will manage this homeland...
... not those who were spoon-fed.
The gold isn't Alişar's. It's the poor's,
the oppressed's.
Alişar came to the Tent and spilt fire!
Gündüz almost died.
Don't you foresee any of these?
If we listened to that tyrant
Alişar's threats...
... we were still sheepherding
in Aleppo, uncle!
Why didn't you come early to
say that to the Banner Lord?
I don't talk with words, I talk
with my sword!
Instructions are yours, actions are
mine, uncle!
Your only action is to get your
uncle in trouble.
I'll take back the Bey's helper duty that
I gave you back!
My loyalty to Kayı is not
limited to duty, Dündar Bey!
We'll see how loyal you are
until tomorrow.
But that's the notice
the Banner Lord gave.
Don't worry about your throne.
I'll bring you Alişar's gold.
My Osman!
Maybe you are right. But what
you're doing...
... isn't right.
Don't worry, aunt.
You'll pray for me in the future, for
what you're calling a mistake today.
I'll go to see my brother.
Aunt.
How's my brother doing?
Bad, Osman.
He didn't wake up yet.
My poor Gündüz. Only if he knew
what his brother did.
What has happened, has happened, Zöhre.
Stop making trouble.
Am I wrong? If he knew, would a valiant
like Gündüz be ambushed like that?
Gündüz. My Gündüz.
I'm begging you, please.
Open your eyes, Gündüz.
Brother!
Thankfully!
Osman.
Brother.
Thankfully!
Alişar... Osman... Kayıs...
How are we going to get out of
all this trouble, Princess?
Stars are quite different from
each other, Helen.
Just like people.
Especially Venus.
It's the most magnificent star
of the endless sky.
We'll be just like Venus.
While the star dies inside the
darkness we're in...
... we'll glow with the light we
get from the sun just like Venus!
Princess Sofia.
Master Yannis sent some news.
Alişar will be here for the night.
Just like you said, Princess.
The Sun sent it's light to Venus again.
Master Yannis has succeeded.
Then start the preparations.
I don't want anything missing.
It's time to show Alişar Venus'
magnificence.
As you say, Princess.
Brother. I have to go.
Osman... Brother...
These scars won't let me stand up now.
If something happens to you while
I'm like this...
... I'll be very upset. Know that.
Don't worry, brother.
Keep calm.
My Osman.
Even the Beys are your enemies now, son.
Don't you worry, Bamsı Bey.
It's time to walk over the enemy.
Thank you, my Osman. The battle is
a valiant's polish.
Otherwise, we'll rust.
To the horses then.
Come here, son.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
We heard about what happened to Gündüz
Bey. We wanted to say get well soon.
Thank you. The arrow missed his heart.
He'll be okay.
But the arrows which hit the heart
open the real wounds.
I have a wound in my hear.
It always bleeds.
I won't apply its cure. I'll let it bleed.
Both love's wound and pain are beautiful.
I'm waiting, Osman.
You're my home in this world.
I'll give you a lifetime of happiness for
the every second you wait.
Be patient.
Keep praying, darling.
- May Allah protect you.
- You too, Osman.
May Allah protect you.
Go.
Konur Alp.
I've been wanting to ask this for a while.
What's with the mark on your eye?
Mongols' work, Sergeant Samsa.
Mongols' work.
It healed. But it seems to me
that the pain is still fresh.
What burns my heart is not the pain.
Its the longing of my brother.
When Osman Bey rescued me from
the Mongol's slave market...
... my brother was with me.
We were together.
He stayed in their hands.
I did my last move to save him.
Only thing I got was a sword in my eye.
Instead of my eye...
... I wish my brother was with me.
My Konur. Do you know anything about
what happened to your brother?
Did you trace him?
Brother, I say, my Boran. Brother, I say.
I looked at every hole, I wandered
through every single Bazaar.
I look for his smell in every wind,
I say his name every time the sun rises.
We poked your wound for nothing.
Forgive us.
It never healed. It keeps bleeding,
Sergeant Samsa.
Keeps bleeding.
We're not the sons of the same father.
We're not the same mother's sons, but...
Although we're not brothers by birth,
we're brothers of the same cause.
We're right? We are!
We fight for our cause.
Death behind us.
Our beliefs in front of us.
It's good to have you, brothers.
It's good to have you. Thank you.
I almost died too. You helped me
a lot then, Ayşe Hatun.
You lightened my burden.
May Allah lighten your burden too.
May Allah heal him. He got up, thankfully.
- Get well soon.
- He got well, thankfully.
Thank you. That's nice of you.
You came all the way to here.
May Allah bless you.
They like our Tent a lot, Ayşe Hatun.
They come here on every chance they get.
That's because they know that
they are loved, my Aygül.
Come on, bring some treats for our guests.
Come on!
My father sends his regards too.
He prays for your health.
May Allah bless your Sheikh.
We're very lucky to receive his prayers.
Our Sheikh should pray more, then. But
we can't get our of troubles.
May Allah protect us all.
A young ant saw a pen writing on
a piece of paper, My Akça.
He then told this secret to another ant.
"The pen is a great craftsman.
I saw it myself" he said.
"It engraved sesame flowers and rose
leaves on the paper."
The other ant stopped suddenly.
"The craftsman is not the pencil,
but the fingers." it said.
Another ant who was listening to them
joined the conversation.
"Neither the fingers nor the pencil."
"The real talent is in the arm." it said.
The old ant who was listening to those
three young ant's conversation...
... couldn't hold himself. "Don't look
for talent in the form." He said.
"It's not about the finger, the
arm, or the power." he said.
"What you call power, gives in to a
temporary death when a being sleeps."
"But the mind always lives." it said.
The talent isn't in the wrist, my Akça.
It's in one's mind.
Indeed, my Sheikh.
There are such situations that you can
not get out of them with force.
There are such foes that you can't
beat them with swords.
Alişar is one of those.
Against him, we'll stand our
ground with ideas...
... and fight with our minds.
He wants chinas for his mansion.
Sharpen your mind's weapon, and
get to work.
Let's see what you can do.
Gather information, my Akça.
Let's see what games...
... that two-faced Alişar is playing.
Certainly, my Sheikh.
We will not allow those who eat
the enemy's food...
... and try to rule the Muslim
lands, my Akça!
We'll be the minds which
no one can enslave...
... of these troublesome lands
we fought for!
I feel refreshed!
Enjoy your meal, Selcan Hatun.
May it heal you.
Why don't you drink it, Bala Hatun?
Didn't you like it?
It's really nice.
I can taste your hands from
the sherbet, Aygül Hatun.
If you need any medicine or
balm, let us now.
We'll send some with the Dervishes.
My mother can make every medicine.
Only if she could make
something that keeps ticks away.
- Aygül!
- Is that wrong, aunt?
Once a tick gets a hold of you,
it's impossible to get rid of it.
Your words are meaningful, Aylül Hatun.
We understand what you mean.
- We bothered you.
- Not at all, my girl.
- Who are you to bother us?
- Aygül!
You very well know who we are.
So you add salt to our sherbet,
then serve us.
We should leave.
We're ready to help, should
you need anything.
Thank you, my girl.
Shame! You're wasting yourself.
Do something about your daughter, Zöhre.
Or I'll have to do it myself!
- Bamsı Bey smelled the battle!
- How couldn't he?
He is an old warrior.
Selamın Aleyküm
(Peace be upon you)
Aleyküm Selam my Bey. Welcome.
(Peace be upon you too)
Thank you. Sergeant Samsa,
is everything ready?
They are, Osman Bey.
Then it's for Allah to decide.
Sıddık! The most important
duty in this battle is yours.
But if you don't want to come, it's okay.
Every sword I swing by you is
my redemption for my past sins.
Don't deny me of this honour, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
My valiant's with Orhun's, Hazar's water
flowing through their veins!
They want to freeze us with
the winter of infidelity...
... and they want to stop us with
their oppression!
Its time we overflow like a river, and
destroy every obstacle in our way!
For the oppressed who reach
the Prophet's...
... level with the wounds
on their hearts...
... for those who wait for the
Turk's justice
For the greatest playmaker!
It's time we destroy the cruel's tricks!
Allahu Ekber!
(Allah is the Greatest)
Is this all, Saltuk Alp?
We could only collect so much
in these hard times, my Bey.
Don't worry. If Osman said he'll find
those golds, he will find them.
Should we trust Osman with the entire
Tent's future, Selcan Hatun?
Should we sit here with our hands tied?
Our hands are not tied. Bowing to that
dog called Alişar is against our laws!
Let's cover the golds with poison
and then give them.
Stop, Selcan Hatun!
He's a Turk Bey. If they learn that we do
this, the Mongols will be on to us.
What if Osman can't bring the gold?
Then Allah knows what we'll do.
There are always guards up ahead.
Go then.
They probably missed you.
Who are you?
Traitor Salvador!
I ran out of the Turks' hands.
I'm here to take shelter.
My Bey. Should we go?
We should stay, brother.
Sıddık knows what to do.
Stop robbing the dead!
You're a Muslim, Sıddık!
Here's the hatch, Osman Bey.
After the hatch, there's a secret
door to the treasure room.
- Where does this lead to?
- To the governor's room.
It's for him to get away if
there's a siege.
Why didn't you tell us in the beginning?
You guys continue, Bamsı Bey.
If this leads to the governor's room,
I should say hi to Sofia.
My Osman, I should come with you.
Your duty is more important, Bamsı Bey.
Take the gold.
- We'll meet here.
- Thank you, Osman.
I should lead the way, there
might be traps.
Why didn't you tell Osman Bey
that there would be traps?
That's the governor's way.
There are no traps there.
Lead the way, Sıddık. Let's go.
Alişar Bey, welcome. Princess Sofia
is waiting for you. Here.
Here's the secret entrance of
the treasure room.
Is there anyone inside?
There's no one inside.
But there are guards at the door.
- How many?
- I don't know.
It's a huge castle's treasure
room after all.
Sıddık! You're sure, right?
You're not leading us to
the dungeon, are you?
No. I'm sure.
I'm your son now, Bamsı Bey.
Say the word and I'll die for you!
You blessed me with bravery.
May you live long.
May Allah bless you in this
world and the afterlife.
Let's go.
Alişar Bey. Welcome.
Here.
While I escape from the dungeon and hardly
save my life, you come to my castle...
... to be honest, it is great courage
You underestimate me Sofia.
I am Alişar Bey.
I came here to lay the foundations of
an unshakeable alliance.
After being deceived by Osman's words?
Be quiet.
The guards might hear us.
While their people are hungry...
... they swim in gold.
Your mother raised you well.
My little lion.
What was that sound?
Theo go check on the room.
Come on valiants, come on.
Open the door. Thieves!
Open the door!
Come on, sons! We can't lose time.
Let's carry these!
Let's carry these all together.
Soldiers, there are thieves!
Open the door!
Soldiers!
Hurry up!
Open the door!
Open the door! I said open the door!
Soldiers!
Take this one too, my son.
Open the door!
We both know all I said is true.
Coming here while you know that shows
you are taking every single risk.
Isn't it worth it?
Of course, it's worth it Alisar Bey...
But I'm the servant of the Byzantine...
... you're the servant of the Seljuks
under the siege of the Mongols.
We are both passionate enough to not
depend on anyone, Sofia.
This is another fact...
... however, there is an obstacle in the
path of our alliance.
For example?
For example, Kayıs.
For example, Edebali.
Open the door! Thieves!
Open the door!
You don't have to carry another one.
There are still lots of them, Sıddık.
This is enough for me.
It is time to close the door.
Sıddık!
Where are you? Open the hatch!
It's the end of the road, Turk!
You all filthy Turks are going to die!
Osman Bey did nothing wrong to you!
Open the hatch now!
You filthy Turks are so naive.
Say hi to Osman Bey!
I am going to kill you Sıddık!
I'll eat you alive!
Though Kayıs are in the control of Söğüt...
...they are only a simple Tent that
belongs to me.
When it comes to Edebali, however,
I don't know why you are scared of him.
He is just a simple merchant in my Bazaar.
That's it.
You also underestimate us, Alişar Bey.
Yes, you are right.
Kayıs are only a simple Tent...
...yet, they are the most important
warriors of the Turks in these lands...
...who are constantly on our path.
And Edebali is only a tout who taunts the
Turks against us.
Being a merchant is only a mask for him.
If you want a strong alliance as you like,
you need to eliminate these two threats.
I need the Ahis and Edebali for economical
benefits.
And, the Kayıs, right now, are busy with
collecting the golds they stole from me.
Alisar Bey, then why are the Mongols
are coming?
I see you are well aware of
every kind of information, Princess.
We also have our own birds, Alişar Bey.
As you know, the greatest power that
exists is to have information.
You are right. The Mongol commander and
his soldiers...
...will be at Söğüt by the morning.
I'll then see how Kayıs behave.
Alişar!
To our alliance, Alişar Bey.
Traitor dog!
Bamsı Bey! Sıddık has just
closed the hatch!
Traitor dog!
Hold on, Bamsı Bey. Hold on!
We need to leave this place as soon as
possible.
Brother Boran, go to the capsule at once
and try to open it. We need to leave.
With the power of Allah, Bamsı Bey.
Let's go!
Open the damn door!
I hope our alliance brings luck to
both of us.
I have no doubts about that.
Our solidarity will be so strong.
Let me escort you to your room.
Princess, I'm sorry to say that I won't
spend the night here.
I need to be present at Tent in the
morning.
Let my soldiers escort you to the exit.
Have a good night, Princess.
Good night.
Traitor dog!
Open the damn door. Thieves!
The door won't stand for too long,
Abdurrahman Gazi. You should get inside.
Bamsı Bey, we can't get the door open.
Bring the spearhead!
Make way! Make way!
My sons! My valiants! Today is the day we
unite with Allah!
Give your last blessings!
May Allah be with us!
Come on, Valiants!
My brothers!
My Osman!
My Bamsı Bey!
Sergeant Samsa!
Magnificent!
Come on! Come on, valiants!
Hold on Valiants! Hold on!
It's good to see you again my Bey!
Konur!
My Osman!
Bamsı Bey!
How could this be?
Who could get into the treasure room like
this?
No way! A secret passage?
Salvador.
It can be nobody but Salvador!
He cooperated with Osman and took
all of our gold.
Here you go.
Brother Abdurrahman, let's go.
Go.
With more force, come on!
Well done.
Sergeant Samsa! Let's go!
Hurry up! We need to get them!
They are downstairs! Go! Get Them! Quick!
My Osman, Salvador betrayed us.
Sıddık has never been Sıddık at all.
One day, we will get revenge, Bamsı Bey.
Let's go!
Damn it!
Are we going to tell this about
Alişar Bey?
For what, so that he can mock us? Never.
He won't know about this.
Follow them!
Then, destroy the passage and let nobody
get inside of this room ever again.
I knew he would do that all along.
That traitor dog!
How many chests are missing?
Three chests are missing, Samsa Bey.
This is still enough for Alişar...
... but we are short on loot.
I was planning to buy new tents.
Don't worry. We will get them
after the next raid, Sergeant Samsa.
I will give some of my shares to you.
After all, Sergeant Samsa's Tent
is our Tent.
With the help of Allah, from tents, we
will move to homes made of stones.
One side of me is thinking about that.
The castle is right here, Konur.
By the way, when are we going to capture
this castle, Osman Bey?
I've been dreaming of conquering for
a while. It's a piece of cake.
Its time will come eventually.
He said I'm a Muslim now.
Recited the shahadah.
He said he'd be my son. He promised me.
He tricked us, Samsa Bey. We will get our
revenge soon.
I freed the murderer of my own son.
I'm the one who tricked myself and for
that I should be ashamed.
There is hope after every incident, Bamsı
Bey.
The time will come.
However, I have bad news for you.
What is it, my Bey?
The Mongols.
What about them, my son?
I heard it while Sofia was talking.
The Mongolians will come to
Söğüt, she said.
After we deal with Alişar, we'll go to
Söğüt to find out what they want.
Let's go.
Princess Sofia.
Please listen to me Princess Sofia.
Despicable dog.
Nothing is as you think.
Traitor.
You stabbed me in the back at
Alişar Bey's mansion.
You told Osman Bey about the secret
passages to treasury room.
No!
They already had the plans of the castle!
How?
Answer my question, you dog!
Edabali.
In order to save my own life, I made them
believe that I became a Muslim.
I infiltrated them and made them trust me.
I didn't have any other options.
I didn't betray master Yannis.
If I wanted, I could just kill your
soldiers and run away with the golds.
Is this true?
Yes, it is true, my Princess. He saved
our lives by pretending to be killing us.
Then he handed us the gold.
They are coming!
You should play dead. And you run away.
Trust me.
In the name of our holy mother Mary, I'm
telling you the truth.
I have a lot to tell you about Osman.
Here you go.
Would you like me to prepare a meal,
my Bey?
Give me the biggest and the most beautiful
room you got.
As you wish, my Bey.
Follow me.
There will be no piece of land where the
shadow of Genghis Khan can't reach.
The legacy of our ancestors will continue
with us.
Let the Kayıs and Alps be forsaken
forever.
Without soul, flesh, humiliated
Tomorrow we'll attack all their Tents and
make suji from their blood...
... boots from their skins...
... jewellery from their honour.
Tomorrow, I want the Tent's Beys.
And Söğüt.
Don't forget every Turk means
twelve gold of tax.
It'd be stupid to slay a
golden egg-laying chickens.
Don't forget why you're here.
To the entertainment and booty!
Alişar Bey is probably all over
Kayı Tent now.
I'll keep him in my hands.
And when my job is done...
... I'll strangle him.
- May I come in?
- Come in.
Master. Akça Dervish is here.
Ahis are with him.
Akça Dervish?
What brought you
to Alişar Bey's mansion?
Our Sheikh ordered. Alişar Bey wanted
to cover his mansion's walls with chinas.
I'm here to examine.
Chinas...
Here. Continue.
Time's up, Dündar Bey!
Tell me. Where's my gold?
The Tent is Kayı's, but the
judgement is yours, Alişar Bey.
Be calm. I'll tell you everything.
Akça Dervish!
Why are you leaving
without saying anything?
Take this gift from Alişar Bey to
Sheikh Edebali.
Thank you.
Take them away.
What's going on here?
Talk now.
I'm listening.
We couldn't gather enough
gold, Alişar Bey.
However, I checked all of our finance.
We are ready to give away all our herds
and rugs.
What can I make out of your useless rugs?
I am talking about gold, Dündar Bey.
Gold!
Didn't I tell you to I'd come and burn
your tribe?
Who can stop me now when I set the stakes
in the middle of the tribe?
And empale your alps?
Who can stop me?
What if I throw you into the
boiling caldrons?
And rip out your lungs?
Who will stop me, Dündar?
Who!?
Osman.
Alişar Bey.
Your gold is outside.
Now leave my tribe alone.
Where are you going without my word?
I kept my promise.
I don't need permission from
anyone to leave.
I am not anyone, Osman.
I am the banner lord.
Will you stop me?
When I say "stop" in this country...
even rain and wind stops.
You'll stop, too Osman!
Stop me if you can!
- Osman!
- Alişar Bey!
Don't go mad.
Osman.
From now on, you can't rule where
I am standing, Alişar Bey.
You shouldn't have disobeyed the
banner lord, Osman.
You are not being a Bey,
at least be an uncle.
Talk it through with Osman.
Otherwise, this will end with blood.
Blood.
From now, nothing will be like before.
Be aware of this.
What does this Alişar mean, father?
Huge trouble is approaching, son.
Huge trouble.
I am hungry.
Thank you.
Today...
We take revenge.
We sacrifice for our ancestors.
Today...
We receive the mighty light from the sun.
We take the Turks'...
joy of life, power...
faith...
from their hands!
Today...
is the day of Balga...
who shapes in flesh and bones...
with Cengiz Han's blood.
Now, go everywhere and tell Balgay's
words.
I came here to impose tax on this land...
enough to make sculpture of me and my
soldiers.
Or...
to take your kids, your wives...
your lives!
Mark my words!
You kept talking about Osman, look
how he brought the gold, Zöhre.
Osman shows us the worst thing first,
then he convinces us to the bad.
- Is this good.
- It is.
Think about what would've happened if
Osman had not been there.
Hatuns. stop quarreling.
Thank Allah, we got over this trouble.
Thank Allah.
What is this noise, uncle?
Father.
It's Mongols.
So, that's what Alişar meant.
I swear on Cengiz.
I swear on the souls in the sky.
If you resists, I'll even kill your
babies.
This country is Mongol's iron fist
Balgay's.
Söğüt is Kayıs'!
Boğaç!
Boğaç! Boğaç!
Brother!
Whoever resist us deserves to die!
I brought you Mongol's martial...
and unending anger.
Dündar...
From now on, you are not a banner lord.
You are just a herd boy, Dündar.
You'll come into Commander Balgay's
presence with Gündüz.
We have brought the Beys who didn't pay
enough taxes, sir.
Aren't we going to participate in the
feast, Commander Balgay?
The feast is going to start when Osman
and his fellas fall into my hands.
Enchain them!
- Zöhre!
- Mother.
The souls in the sky and underground gave
us everything.
The only thing they didn't give to us is
the feeling of mercy.
Aunt!
Take them!
Father.
The alps who attack to the Nökers from
Cengiz's blessed blood.
Your courage is unbelievable.
We've hard that...
Kayıs forgot Mongol's anger in Söğüt.
We have come to remind you
who rules here.
Drown in Cengiz's blood, dog!
Protect us my Allah.
Kill all the Alps!
Kill everyone who resists!
Mongols have come, my Bey.
Why are you running, bre!
Is it appropriate to run from death?
They running like a headless sheep.
Neck or nothing, Sergeant Samsa!
Let's remind them Turk's power.
It has been a long time since I killed one
of them.
It's going to be a fun, Bamsı Bey.
Allah is eternal!
The flag represents Turks' independence.
We break those who intend to harm it.
This is Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman's word.
- Remember this.
- Osman Bey.
- Speaks in an old language -
Turks' Beys are going to fall like rain.
They'll seek mercy.
"May Ovoo bless every stone and tree
with blood."
Kill them all!
Balgay. Osman is standing against our
soldiers with his Alps.
They killed Nökers.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Osman smelled us.
The prey is here.
Bring him here at once.
Balgay wants Osman.
Balgay waits for Osman.
Don't mercy whoever resists.
My Osman, what those crickets want
from you?
Let's see what's wrong with Balgay.
Lower your weapon, Osman Bey.
Your Alps, too.
Alps!
Drop your weapon.
My Osman said Alişar's gold is coming from
Konya.
The owner of the gold we took from the
caravanserai is now clear, Bamsı Bey.
They took the gold back. But, it's now clear
that those dogs we killed are Balgay's.
are Balgay's.
It's not about the gold or soldiers.
Balgay has something else in mind.
Caravanserai was raided, and now we know
who is Alişar with.
That's what Osman wanted to reveal.
May Allah bless us with an honorable death,
Bamsı Bey.
May Allah grant us with killing those guys
with our bare hands before we die.
- Amin, brother, amin.
- Eyvallah, son. Eyvallah (may it be).
Sit down.
- Speaks in an old language -
There is always better,
there is always a stronger one.
We have a lot of enemies because of
our manhood.
Your grandfather is Suleyman Shah.
Your father is Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Now, it's you.
My breed goes back to Oguz Kagan.
You can't even count in your lifespan.
If I intend to kill you, I'd spend my
least important...
soldier on you.
If I want to buy you...
Even Cengiz Han's treasures wouldn't be
enough.
Then, give me my sword back so that I
can take your head.
While there are so many heads you'll take,
fights you'll have...
castles you'll conquer...
why would you consider Balgay's head?
I studied you very well, Osman Bey.
How do you think you'll buy me?
By whetting your greed which is as
great as...
the Khan Tengri Mountain...
and as great as Gobi Desert.
Tell me.
Let's just cut to the case.
What do you mean?
Listen to me very carefully, Osman Bey.
I bid you death...
to you and your brothers outside.
By my will, or by fighting.
You choose.
Die now, or be my banner lord.
And shake the whole world.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com